const quizQuestions = [
    {
        img:
        question: "Who invented the Chinese torture box?",
        answers: {
            a: "David Blaine",
            b: "David Copperfield",
            c: "Harry Houdini"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        img:  
        question: "What is Mario Bros daytime job?",
        answers: {
            a: "A Race Car Driver",
            b: "A Teacher",
            c: "A Plumber"
         },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        img: 
        question: "Who is Tim Burton?",
        answers: {
            a: "Director",
            b: "Singer",
            c: "Actor",
         },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "Which is the name of the bird in the movie UP?",
        answers: {
            a: "Karl",
            b: "Kevin",
            c: "Sam"
      },
      correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "How old was Michael Jackson when he died?",
        answers: {
            a: "47",
            b: "55",
            c: "50"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "Where does Pooh live?",
        answers: {
            a: "A Tree",
            b: "A Mushroom",
            c: "A House"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "How old is Rapunzel in the movie ‘Tangled’?",
        answers: {
            a: "18",
            b: "15",
            c: "20"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "What year did ‘Thriller’ come out?",
        answers: {
            a: "1980",
            b: "1982",
            c: "1988"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "Which game won the VGX award in 2013?",
        answers: {
            a: "Grand Theft Auto V",
            b: "PubG",
            c: "League Of Legends"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        img:
        question: "Who played the character of Edward Scissorhands?",
        answers: {
            a: "Johnny Depp",
            b: "Paul Newman",
            c: "Humphrey Bogart"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    }
  ];
  export { quizQuestions };

